(mysterious music begins)
- I think... I think when it's all over
it just comes back in flashes, you know?
It's like a kaleidoscope of memories,
it just all comes back.
But he never does.
I think part of me knew
the second I saw him
that this would happen.
It's not really anything
he said or anything he did,
it was the feeling that
came along with it.
And the crazy thing is I don't know
if I'm ever gonna feel that way again,
but I don't know if I should.
I knew his world moved too
fast and burned too bright,
but I just thought,
how can the devil be
pulling you toward someone
who looks so much like an
angel when he smiles at you?
Maybe he knew that when he saw me.
I guess I just lost my balance.
I think that the worst part
of it all wasn't losing him
it was losing me.
(Upbeat pop song begins)
♪ Once upon a time ♪
♪ A few mistakes ago ♪
♪ I was in your sights ♪
♪ You got me alone ♪
♪ You found me ♪
♪ I guess you didn't care ♪
♪ And I guess I liked that ♪
♪ And when I fell hard ♪
♪ You took a step back ♪
♪ Without me ♪
♪ And he's long gone ♪
♪ When he's next to me ♪
♪ And I realize ♪
♪ The blame is on me ♪
♪ 'Cause I knew you were
trouble when you walked in ♪
♪ So shame on me now ♪
♪ Flew me to places I'd never been ♪
♪ 'Til you put me down, oh ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in ♪
♪ So, shame on me now ♪
♪ Flew me to places I'd never been ♪
♪ Now I'm lyin' on the cold hard ground ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble ♪
♪ No apologies ♪
♪ He'll never see you cry ♪
♪ Pretends he doesn't know ♪
♪ That he's the reason why ♪
♪ You're drowning ♪
♪ And I heard you moved on ♪
♪ From whispers on the street ♪
♪ A new notch in your belt ♪
♪ Is all I'll ever be ♪
♪ And now I see ♪
♪ Now I see ♪
♪ He was long gone ♪
♪ When he met me ♪
♪ And I realize ♪
♪ The joke is on me, hey ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in (oh) ♪
♪ So shame on me now ♪
♪ Flew me to places I'd never been ♪
♪ 'Til you put me down, oh ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in ♪
♪ So shame on me now ♪
♪ Flew me to places I'd never been, yeah ♪
♪ Now I'm lyin' on the cold hard ground ♪
♪ Oh, oh (yeah) ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble, (oh) ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble ♪
♪ And the saddest fear ♪
♪ Comes creepin' in ♪
♪ That you never loved me ♪
♪ Or her ♪
♪ Or anyone ♪
♪ Or anything ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in ♪
♪ So shame on me now ♪
♪ Flew me to places I'd
never been (never been) ♪
♪ 'Til you put me down, oh ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in ♪
♪ (knew it right there) ♪
♪ So shame on me now
(knew it right there) ♪
♪ Flew me to places I'd never been ♪
♪ (Ooh) now I'm lyin' on
the cold hard ground ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble (oh) ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble ♪
♪ I knew you were trouble
when you walked in ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble, trouble ♪
I don't know if you know who you are
until you lose who you are.